Murder Victims Families for Reconciliation; Records apap313
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Events, 1992-2003, Undated; 4; 3 cubic ft.
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - List of Presenters, 2001; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 54)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Mailing Materials, 2001; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 55)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Media Plan, 2000 (Oversized 1, Folder 11)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Media Plan, 2001; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 56)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Plans, 2001; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 57)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Plenary Session Evaluations, Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 58)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Programs, 2001; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 59)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Proposal, 1999-2000; Undated (Box 1 (4-Events), Folder 60)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Registration Forms, 2001; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 1)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Registration List, Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 2)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Remembrance Ceremony Cards, Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 3)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Save Date Cards, 2000; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 4)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Sessions 1QA and B Evaluations, Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 5)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Sessions 2 A, B, and C Evaluations, Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 6)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Sessions 3A, B, C, and E Evaluations, Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 7)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Sessions 4A, B, C, and E Evaluations, Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 8)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Sessions 5B, C, D, E, and F Evaluations, Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 9)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Sessions A, B, C, E, and F Evaluations, Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 10)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Sessions 7A, B, C, E, and F Evaluations, Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 11)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Unsorted Session Evaluations, Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 12)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Vendor Table Requests, Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 13)
  - Healing the Wounds of Murder - Working Group, 1999; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 14)
  - Illinois Communication Campaign, 2002-2003; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 15)
  - Journey of Hope, 1994 (Vhs 3)
  - Journey of Hope California, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 17)
  - Journey of Hope California, 1995; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 18)
  - Journey of Hope California, 1995 (Oversized 1, Folder 12)
  - Journey of Hope California - Pat Bane's File, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 19)
  - Journey of Hope Georgia, 1993-1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 20)
  - Journey of Hope Georgia, 1994 (Oversized 1, Folder 13)
  - Journey of Hope Georgia - Evaluations, Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 21)
  - Journey of Hope Georgia - Press, 1994; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 22)
  - Journey of Hope Indiana, 1992-1995; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 23)
  - Journey of Hope - Pins, Undated (Artifact-box 1, Item 1)
  - Journey of Hope Organization Handbook, 1994; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 24)
  - Journey of Hope Photos, 1998; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 25)
  - Journey of Hope - Not In My Name, Undated (Vhs 4)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia, 1994; 1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 26)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - 21 Day Rule Petition, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 27)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Budget, 1995-1995; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 28)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Contacts, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 29)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Evening with Sister Helen Prejean, Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 30)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Event Applications for October 1st and 2nd, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 31)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Event Applications for October 3rd-6th, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 32)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Event Applications for September 21st and 22nd, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 33)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Event Applications for September 23rd, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 34)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Event Applications for September 24th, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 35)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Event Applications for September 25th and 26th, Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 36)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Event Applications for September 27th and 28th, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 37)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Event Applications for September 29th, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 38)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Event Applications for September 30th, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 39)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Event Evaluations, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 40)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Finances, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 41)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Flyers, 1994; 1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 42)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Grant Applications, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 43)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - List of T-Shirt and Video Orders, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 44)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Maps and Directions, Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 45)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Meetings, 1994-1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 46)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Notes, Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 47)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Orientation and Gathering Arrangements, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 48)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Orientation and Gathering Liability Insurance, Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 49)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Permits, Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 50)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Preliminary Report, Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 51)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Press Release and Brochure, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (4-Events), Folder 52)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Registration Information, Undated (Box 3 (4-Events), Folder 1)
  - Journey of Hope Virginia - Schedules, 1996; Undated (Box 3 (4-Events), Folder 2)
  - Kentucky Tour, 1999-2000; Undated (Box 3 (4-Events), Folder 3)
  - "Life After Death Row" - Raw Footage, Chicago (December 8th) - Tape #V37, 2002 (Vhs 5)
  - "Life After Death Row" - Raw Footage, Chicago (December 8th) - Tape #V38, 2002 (Vhs 6)
  - Lifelines Conference, 1994 (Oversized 1, Folder 14)
  - Lifelines Conference, 1994-1996; Undated (Box 3 (4-Events), Folder 4)
  - March for Moratorium Photos, Undated (Box 3 (4-Events), Folder 5)
  - Massachusetts Citizens Against the Death Penalty Award Ceremony, 1999 (Box 3 (4-Events), Folder 6)
  - Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation Event Photos featuring Mike Farrell, 2002 (Box 3 (4-Events), Folder 7)
  - Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation Event Phots with Martin Sheen, 1994 (Box 3 (4-Events), Folder 8)
  - Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation Wedding- Kenilworth Union Church, 2002 (Box 3 (4-Events), Folder 9)
  - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty Conference, 1997; Undated (Box 3 (4-Events), Folder 10)
  - National Commission on Capital Punishment-Human Rights Hearings, 1996; Undated (Box 3 (4-Events), Folder 11)
  - National Death Penalty Abolitionist Strategy Meeting, Undated (Box 3 (4-Events), Folder 12)
  - National Innocence Network Conference, 2005; Undated (Box 3 (4-Events), Folder 13)
  - National organization for Victim Assistance Conference, 2001; Undated (Box 3 (4-Events), Folder 14)
  - New York Visit, 1995; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 3 (4-Events), Folder 15)
  - New York Visit-Pat Bane's Resources, 1995-1998; Undated (Box 3 (4-Events), Folder 16)
  - New York Visit, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 15)
  - "Not In Our Name" - New England Speaking Tour Contacts, 1998-1999 (Box 3 (4-Events), Folder 17)
  - "Not In Our Name" (April 4th), 2003 (Vhs 7)
  - Oklahoma Ray of Hope Visit, Undated (Box 3 (4-Events), Folder 18)
  - Oregon Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Annual Meeting, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 3 (4-Events), Folder 19)
  - People of Faith Against the Death Penalty Training Conference, 1996; Undated (Box 3 (4-Events), Folder 20)
  - People of Faith Against the Death Penalty - Training Workshop, 1998 (Oversized 1, Folder 16)
  - Press Conference - Call for Moratorium on the Death Penalty at Northeastern University December 3, 2002, Undated (Box 3 (4-Events), Folder 21)
  - Resolve to Stop Violence, 1997-1998; Undated (Box 4 (4-Events), Folder 1)
  - Restorative Justice Conference, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 4 (4-Events), Folder 2)
  - San Francisco Report Photos, Undated (Box 4 (4-Events), Folder 3)
  - Student Death Penalty Conference, Undated (Box 4 (4-Events), Folder 4)
  - Unidentified Event Photos, Undated (Box 4 (4-Events), Folder 5)
  - University of Cincinnati-Death Penalty on Trial: Legal and Social Perspectives, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 4 (4-Events), Folder 6)
  - University of Maryland-Capital Punishment Panel Discussion, 1997; Undated (Box 4 (4-Events), Folder 7)
  - Vatican Visit, 2003; Undated (Box 4 (4-Events), Folder 8)
  - Walkin' to New Orleans- Sam Sheppard, 1995; Undated (Box 4 (4-Events), Folder 9)
  - Wrongful Conviction Conference, 1998 (Box 4 (4-Events), Folder 10)
- Subject Files, 1981-2007, Undated; 5; 4.2 cubic ft.
  Series 5 contains reference materials that Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation have used in their fight against the death penalty. While many of the materials broadly deal with the death penalty, there are a number of items that record the work of other anti-death penalty advocates and organizations. Along with these materials, there are also documents relating to court proceedings and legislative hearings. Contained in this series are newspaper clippings, press releases, newsletters, flyers, pamphlets, booklets, brochures, manuscripts, transcripts, drafts, correspondence, court proceedings, legislative bills, amici curiae, floppy disks, zip disks, dvds, cds, and vhs tapes.
  - Adair County Kentucky, 2003 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Airlie Conference, Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Alliance for Justice Newsletter and Flyers, 1998; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - American Bar Association, 2000-2001; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - American Friends Service Committee Press Release, Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - "American Prospect" Article, 2000; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Amicus Brief of Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation for the State of Nebraska Vs. Nebraska Board of Pardons, Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Amnesty International, 1996; 1999-2000; 2007; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Amnesty International - Death Penalty Report, 1994; 1996; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Amnesty International USA - "U.S. Campaign Againts the Death Penalty", Undated (Vhs 8)
  - Arkansas Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1998; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Arkansas Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1998 (Oversized 1, Folder 17)
  - "Balancing the Scales", Undated (Dvd 3)
  - "Balancing the Scales: Texas Moratorium", Undated (Vhs 9)
  - Bane, Pat - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty Resignation, 1996 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Bane, Pat - Newspaper Clippings, 1981; 1985-1994; 1996-1997; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Bellow, Clifton-Anti-Death Penalty Speech, 2000 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Bennington Ads, 1999-2000; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Blue Mountain Arts Group, Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Bridges, Ken, 2003 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Brochures and Flyers, 1994; 2004-2005; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - California Indian Radio Project - "Honoring Our Grief: Healing the Wounds", Undated (Cassette 3)
  - "Capital Punishment and Contemporary Values", 1993 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - "The Case Against the Death Penalty", Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - "The Case for Putting Victims in the Constitution", Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Catholics Against Capital Punishment Newsletter, 2001; 2003 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - CRR, Undated (Floppy-disk 32)
  - Celebrate the Children of Resistance, 2003 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Conferences, 1991; 1994-1998; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Criminal Victimization Survey, 2003 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Cushing, Renny, Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Cushing V. McLaughlin, 2001; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Dead Man Walking - Newspaper Clippings, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Deans, Marie, Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - "The Death Game: Capital Punishment and the Luck of the Draw", 2003 (Cd 1)
  - Death Penalty Abolitionists Conferences, 1997 (Oversized 1, Folder 18)
  - Death Penalty and Children, 1998; 2000; 2003-2004; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - The Death Penalty and the Media, Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Death Penalty and Physicians, 1994 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Death Penalty Facts, 1995-1998; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - "The Death Penalty in Black and White", 1998 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Death Penalty Information Center, 1992; 1994; 1997; 2007 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Death Penalty Polling, 1999 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - The Death Penalty: The Religious Community Call for Abolition, 1998; 2000; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - "Death without Justice", 2001 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - "Disarming the State's Lethal Weapon", 2002 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - "Double Justice: Race and Capital Punishment", 1993 (Vhs 10)
  - Dules Airport Photos, 1999; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Eaton, Dennis, 1998; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Economical Criminal Justice Gathering, 1997; 2000-2001 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Elijah, Soffiyah, 2000; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Equal Rights of Crime Victims Act- Texas, 2003; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - "Evolving Standards of Decency: The Juvenile Death Penalty in the United States"- A Resource Kit, Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Family Law, 2001 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - "Facing the Enemy: The Jo Tuffnell Story", Undated (Vhs 11)
  - Federal Death Penalty Abolition Act, 1999; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Fellowship, 2000; 2003 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - "Finney Keeps Word on Death Penalty", 1994 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - First Response to Victims of Crime, 2000 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Florida, 1997; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Florida State University Law Review, 1999 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - "The Forgotten Population", 2004 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - "Forgotten Victims" Video, Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Friends Committee on National Legislation, 2000 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Gayle, Aba, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Gibson, Greg, 2000; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Hill, Zane, 1998; Undated (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Homicide Survivors, 2004 (Oversized 1, Folder 19)
  - "Human Rights Human Wrongs: Sentencing Children to Death", 2003 (Box 1 (5-Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - Identified Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation Member Photos, 1996-2000; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Illinois Commission on Capital Punishment, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Illinois Death Penalty Commutation Cases, 2002; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Innocence Protection Act, 1999-2001; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Innocence Protection Act - C-SPAN (February 11th), 2000 February 11 (Vhs 12)
  - Innocence Protection Act - Media Coverage, 2000 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Interfaith Coalition to Stop Executions, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Jaeger, Marietta, 1994; 1999-2000; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Juvenile Death Penalty, 2004 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Kansas, 1994-1995; 1997-1999; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Kentucky Racial Justice Act, 1998 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - "Kids are Different: The Juvenile Death Penalty in the United States"-Resource Kit, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Kyles, Curtis, 1997 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Laffin, Art, 2000; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Lamm, Audrey and Gus - "Her Mother's Daughter", Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 20)
  - Lamm Case-Nebraska, 2000; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - "Last Breath", Undated (Vhs 13)
  - Langley, Rick-Murder Trial, 2003; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Leadership Conference, 1998; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Lowerstein, Thomas, 1997; 1999 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Lucero, Bill- Testimony in Opposition to Kansas Senate Bill 166, 1999 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - "Making Your Case: Elements of a Successful Media Campaign", Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Malo, Eve, 2000 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Managing Grief, 1995-1997; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Marshall, Larry- Testimony on Wrongful Conviction, 1999 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Massachusetts, 1984; 1997; 1999; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Mathis, Teresa, 1984; 1989-1991; 1994; 1996; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - McCarthy, Carolyn, 1995; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - "Mercy and Justice: On Capital Punishment", Undated (Vhs 14)
  - Misc, Undated (Floppy-disk 33)
  - Misc, Undated (Floppy-disk 34)
  - Montgomery County Volunteer Jail Chaplaincy Dinner, 1999 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Moratorium Campaign, 2000; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Moussaoui, Zacarias, 2001; 2005 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Murder Victims' Families for Human Rights, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation member Personal Stories, 1995-2002; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty Piece (September 5th), 2001 (Floppy-disk 35)
  - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty - Texas, 1996-1997; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty - Texas Pat Bane's References, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Nebraska Legislative Bill on Victims' Rights, 2001 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Neighbors Who Care - Washington D.C., Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - "New Directions from the Field: Victims' Rights and Services for the 21st Century", Undated (Vhs 15)
  - New Hampshire, 1997-1998; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - "New Hampshire Citizens' Criminal Justice Attitudes and Punishment Preferences", 2000 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - New Hampshire House of Representatives- Vote on Abolishing the Death Penalty, 2000 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - New Jersey - Death Penalty Outline for Defense Attorneys, 2000 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - New Jersey - Death Penalty Study Commission, 2007 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - New Jersey - Miscarriages of Justice Conference Paper, "On the Conviction of the Innocent", 2000 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - New Jersey Public Policy Research Institute-Final Report on Meeting the Challenge of Prisoner Reentry, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - New Jerseyans for Alternative to the Death Penalty, 2007; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalty - Pins, Undated (Artifact-box 1, Item 1)
  - New York - Anti-Death Penalty Letter, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1994; 1996-1997; 1999-2003; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Florida, 1997-1998; 2000; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Georgia, 2001 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Newspaper and Magazine Clippings, 1997 (Flat-file 1, Folder 1)
  - Ogletree, Charles, 1999 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Ohio State Law Journal-When Legislatures Delegate Death, 2002 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Peace Works, 1999 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Pennsylvania Senate Judiciary Committee - Public Hearing on Senate Bill 952 (1 of 2), 2000 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Pennsylvania Senate Judiciary Committee - Public Hearing on Senate Bill 952 (2 of 2), 2000 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Pennsylvania - Witness Testimony for Senate Bill 952, 2000; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Prejean, Helen - Annual Public Address, 1999 (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Prejean, Helen - Photos with Renny Cushing, 1998; Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Preliminary Report on the State of the Death Penalty in Illinois in the Year of the Moratorium, Undated (Box 2 (5-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Prison Ministry Forum, 2008; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Prison Ministry Photos, Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Prisoners' Stories, 1995-1998; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Redeem the Dream, 2000; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Randy Reeves, Undated (Vhs 16)
  - Reg - Vanderslice, Undated (Floppy-disk 36)
  - Reference Materials - Ohio, 1990; 1992; 1994-1996; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Religious Belief and the Death Penalty, 1996; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Religious Community's Response to Timothy McVeigh's Execution, 2001; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Religious Organizing Against the Death Penalty, 2000; 2002; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Report of the First National Symposium on Crime Victims as Witnesses to an Execution, 1999 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Rice, Bob and Gail, 2000-2001; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Sampson, Gary, 2002-2003; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Southern Center for Human Rights, Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - State Actions - Arkansas, 1994-1997; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - State Actions - Minnesota, Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - State Actions - New York, 1991; 1993-1998; Undated (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - State Actions - New York, 1995-1996 (Oversized 1, Folder 21)
  - State of Ohio Vs. Ediberto Huertas - Writ of Certiorari to the Supreme Court of Ohio, 1990 (Box 3 (5-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Statement made before the Connecticut Commission on the Death Penalty, 2002 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Stephanie Roper Committee and Foundation, 2000 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Strategies for Abolishing the Death Penalty, 1999 (Box 4 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)